

Olaoluwayemi Rasheed

Software Engineer

My goal is to become associated with a company where I can utilize my skills and gain further experience while enhancing the company's productivity and reputation. This I believe, makes me best suited for the internship position that is being offered at Linux Jobber as a web developer.

rasholayemi@gmail.com

bit.ly/rasholayemidev

twitter.com/YemiTumininu

in linkedin.com/in/olaoluwayemi-rasheed-059216177

github.com/Yemiemy

WORK EXPERIENCE

Coding Instructor Square College 🗷

02/2020 - Present

Lekki, Lagos

- Educated students on Arduino and Programming applying variety of instructional techniques, including hands-on curriculum.
- Provided instructional materials to facilitate learning.
- Implemented and optimized new curriculum and day-to-day instruction to align educational strategies with industry best practices.

Contact: Mrs Somorin - 07056400311

Web Developer

ArtisanGet 🗷 12/2019 - Present

Yaba, Lagos

one-stop service provider company for all homes and offices repair and maintenance.

Achievements/Tasks

- Created site layout and user interface using HTML and CSS practices and Django for the backend.
- Took concepts and produced design mockups and prototypes to strengthen designs, enhance user experiences and improve site interactions.

Robotics Instructor Gate Academy

07/2019 - 08/2019

Yaba, Lagos.

Achievements/Tasks

 Improved operations by drafting and implementing training materials for systems users, systems service and maintenance processes.

Contact: Mr Tobi - +234 802 292 8390

Software Instructor Odecazdeo

09/2019 - 11/2019

Akoka, Lagos,

Achievements/Tasks

• Taught C#, C++ and Python coding languages according to age group and ability.

EDUCATION

Systems Engineering University of Lagos

SKILLS Diango

AWS Cloud Computing Python CSS3 **Hosting Service SEO Email Marketing**

MS Office

Creative Thinking

Arduino

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Online Portfolio (06/2020 – 06/2020) 🗗

Created an online portfolio for myself.

Online shoe store (05/2019 – 07/2019) 🗹

An e-commerce store that allows payment online for the purchase of goods.

LocalMan Finder (05/2020 – Present)

A search app for the locality.

Task manager app (09/2019 - 09/2019)

A task manager app built during a DSC hackhathon.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Worked on many projects in the span of six months (01/2020 - 06/2020)

Deployed apps I built and apps built by others

Finished AWS Cloud Computing Course (06/2020 - 06/2020)

Course by Udemy

LANGUAGES

Yourba

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

10/2017 - Present

Akoka, Yaba